hotjoomlatemplates.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy - HotThemes

HotThemes values the privacy and security of the information that you share with us through www.hotjoomlatemplates.com (the “Web Site”).  It is important that you understand how we collect, use, and maintain your information.

**Privacy** \- Any and all of the information collected on this site, including personal and business information and email addresses, will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or otherwise distributed. "Personal and business information" include name, company name, address, telephone number and account username and password.

**How we store your data -** All personal information you submit is encrypted and secure. We keep information in MySQL database only.

**Safety** \- We do not collect or store credit card, bank account and other financial information! All orders are processed using secure checkout through our credit card processors (Paypal and 2checkout). At no time does HotThemes ever possess your credit card or bank account number!

**Newsletter opt-in** \- After opening an account on this site, you would be opt-in to our monthly newsletter. In this newsletter, we promote our new products and inform our members about news on our site, bug fixes of our products and special promotions. It's important to be subscribed because of the nature of our service. In example, without subscription, you won't know when new template is released or when important bug fix is released. Therefore, you can miss your chance to download it until your account is active. Your email address will never be shared with 3rd parties!

**Newsletter opt-out** \- On every newsletter email that we send, you may find a link that allows you to opt-out anytime. If you opt-out your account will still be active on our site, but you would not receive further newsletter emails from us.

**Cookies** \- We use cookies on this website. By using this site, you agree that we may store and access cookies on your device.

**Delete your data** \- If you would like to delete your account from our server, please [contact us](https://hot-themes.com/members/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=2) and ask for removal of your data. After your request is processed, all data about you stored on our server will be deleted forever without possibility to be restored.

**Policy updates** \- We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective upon posting.  Please check back periodically for updates. If at any point we decide to use Personal Information in a manner that is materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users have a choice to request their data to be deleted from our database by contacting us at any time.

**We respect your privacy!**

_Last Updated: May 7, 2018_
